Standing in the door I could see...
站在门口 我可以看到
...the lights on the drop zone...
降落区的灯光
...and I had to assume that was our drop zone...
我必须假设那就是降落区
...way in the ahead of us.
在我们前面很远的地方
And so that we had the red light...
所以 红灯亮了
...I had everybody standing up ready to jump.
我让所有人起立 准备跳伞
So, when the plane started to get hit...
所以当飞机遭遇攻击时
...and suddenly the pilot gives me the green light...
突然间 驾驶给我们绿灯讯号
...I'm out the door immediately.
我立刻就跳出门了
We got such an opening blast from the opening shot...
我们突然遭到降落伞打开以及螺旋浆...
...from the prop blast that it broke this chin strap that we had on this helmet liner.
强大气流的冲击 钢盔的带子都断了
And that's when I lost this famous leg bag...
我就是在这时候失去那个著名的...
...that everybody talks about...
大家都在谈论着的腿袋
...just from the shock of the opening.
因为开伞的震力
It just flew right off my foot.
它就这样飞离了我的腿
We came from the sky.
我们从空中而来
We hit, and in any direction you went...
触地 四面八方...
...there would be enemy, you knew it.
都有敌人 你早就心里有数
And that was all part of what you accepted.
这些是你必须坦然面对的
How do you prepare yourself mentally?
你如何做好心理准备?
Each man must do that himself.
每个人都得靠自己做好准备
Each man must prepare himself mentally to make that jump.
每个人都必须为跳伞做好心理准备
At the back of your mind you, you know, you wonder what will happen and all that.
你心里会盘算着会发生什么事等等
You know you've been trained and trained and trained...
你不停的接受训练
...and what your job is gonna be...
好让你明白将来的任务
...and what you're supposed to do and...
你该怎么应付状况
Oh, that's what you gotta think about, you know?
这些都是你要去想的
And we lost a lot of people that night...
我们那晚失去很多人
...but you try to put it all out of your mind.
但是..必须努力忘却这些事
Give me a light.
史密斯 借个火
Lip, did Evans make it?
李普! 依凡斯加入了吧?
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
He's in Lieutenant Meehan's stick, sir.
他在米汉中尉那里
Lieutenant Meehan!
米汉中尉
Will, could use some help.
威尔需要帮忙
Will.
威尔!
Will, I need your help here.
威尔 我需要你帮忙
Get ready!
准备好!
Stand up!
起立!
Hook up!
上勾!
Equipment check!
检查装备!
Sound off for equipment check!
报告装备检查!
Ten okay!
十号就绪!
Nine okay!
九号就绪!
Eight okay!
八号就绪!
Seven okay!
七号就绪!
Six okay!
六号就绪!
Five okay!
五号就绪!
Four okay!
四号就绪!
Three okay!
三号就绪!
Two okay!
二号就绪!
One okay!
一号就绪!
Jesus Christ! Let's go, let's go!
天啊! 我们快跳!
Does that light look green to you?
你看那是绿灯吗?
No, let's go!
快跳!
I'm hit!
我被击中了!
Jesus, tell Meehan to get them out of there!
天啊! 叫米汉送人出去!
Ahh!
啊!
2:00!
两点钟方向!
Oh, Jesus Christ!
我的天啊
Go!
跳!
I wanna jump, sir!
我要跳伞 长官
Now, listen to me, stay on the plane...
听我说 留在飞机上
...you're not jumping!
你不准跳
He's okay.
他没事
No, sir, no!
长官 快跳!
All right, son of a bitch.
好吧 混蛋
Where's the goddamn DZ?
降落区到底在哪里?
Maybe it's three more minutes on this bearing!
大概保持这方向再三分钟!
We get any lower...
我们再降低的话
...we ain't gonna need any frigging parachutes!
就不需要降落伞了!
Slow down!
慢一点!
We gotta get some altitude!
我们必须飞高点!
They can't jump at this speed!
他们不能在这种速度下跳伞
We there?
我们到了没?
Oh, God!
天啊!
Oh, no!
不要!
Let's go!
走吧!
Flash!
电闪!
Shit!
该死!
I don't think that's the correct reply, trooper.
士兵 你不该那样回应的
I say "flash", you say "thunder".
我说"电闪" 你就该说"雷鸣"
Yes, sir, thunder, sir.
是的 长官! "雷鸣" 长官!
Musette bag.
野战背包
Coach?
教练?
Sir, it's Hall, sir.
长官 我是赫尔
I was on the basketball team.
我曾在你的篮球队上
Leg bag?
腿袋呢?
Prop blast got it, sir...
气流把它吹掉了 长官
...and my radio and batteries with it.
我的无线电与电池也在里面
Mine, too.
我的也是
Mine are somewhere behind those trees.
大概落在那些树丛后面
Okay.
好了
Follow me.
跟着我
To hell with that!
怎么回事!
Wait until they reload.
等他们重新上膛
Go.
走
Aren't you D Company?
你不是Ｄ连的吗?
Able, sir.
Ａ连 长官!
Guess that means one of us is in the wrong drop zone, sir?
看来有人降错降落区了
Yeah, or both of us.
又或许我们两个都降错了
Do you have a weapon, sir?
你有武器吗 长官?
Just my knife.
只有我的佩刀
Do you have any idea where we are, sir?
你知道我们在哪里吗 长官?
Some.
大概知道
So, you're a radioman?
你是通信兵?
Yes, sir.
是的
Well, I was until I lost my radio on the jump.
至少在我跳伞丢掉无线电前是的
I'm sure I'll get chewed out for that.
我一定会被痛骂一顿
Well, if you were in my platoon...
如果你在我排里
...I'd tell you you were a rifleman first, radioman second.
我会说你先是名步兵 然后才是通信兵
Maybe you could tell that to my platoon leader...
或许你可以告诉我的排长
...when we find him.
当我们找到他时
If we find him.
如果能找到他
It's a deal.
就这样说定了
First, I need your help.
首先我需要你帮忙
We'll locate some landmarks to get our bearings.
我们要找些地标来辨明方位
Keep your eyes peeled for buildings, farmhouses...
睁大眼睛找建筑物 农舍...
...bridges, roads, trees.
桥梁 道路 还有树!
I wonder if the rest of them are as lost as we are.
不知其他人是否也跟我们一样迷路
We're not lost, Private.
我们没迷路
We're in Normandy.
我们在诺曼底啊
Who's that?
那是谁?
Lieutenant Winters, is that you?
温特斯中尉? 是你吗?
Get in here, sit down.
过来 坐下
Any weapon?
有武器吗?
No, sir.
没有 长官
As soon as I hit the prop blast, so long leg bag.
我一被气流吹到 腿袋就不见了
All I got is this knife and some TNT.
我只有这把刀和一些炸药
These 82nd boys got their M-1s, though.
不过82师的伙伴们有M1步枪
Oh, man, 82nd, where the hell are we?
天啊 82师 我们在哪里啊?
Sir, I saw a sign back thataways.
我在后面看到一个路标
It said, "Sainte-Mere-Eglise".
上面说"圣梅利格里斯"
Flashlight.
手电筒
Raincoat?
雨衣
You got a raincoat? Yeah.
你有雨衣吗? 有的
We're about seven kilometers away from our objective.
我们大约离目的地七公里远
And four hours from when we need to have it secured.
还有四小时可以去攻占那个区域
So, we got a lot of walking ahead of us.
我们还有很多路要走
You men will stick with us until we find your unit.
你们找到自己部队前跟着我
Let's go.
走吧
Hey, Sarge, where are we going?
士官 我们去哪里?
Causeway Number Two, Utah Beach.
二号堤道 犹他海滩
The Germans flooded the fields inland.
内陆到处是德军
We don't clear the routes, we ain't moving.
我们不清除那里 部队就无路可走
Five of us ain't gonna secure a road.
我们五个人无法守卫一条路
That Louie don't even have a weapon.
那中尉连武器都没有
I don't remember hearing about any railroads near our objective.
我不记得目的地有任何铁路
I'm telling you...
我告诉你
...this is the spur line that runs parallel to the river.
这是与河道平行的铁路支线
We should be nearing a road and bridge.
前面应该有条路和一座桥
Yeah, how would you know?
你怎么知道?
Because I studied sand tails, all right?
我研究过沙盘 好吧?
Probably a frigging train or...
可能是火车或
Flash.
电闪
Thunder.
雷鸣
Lieutenant, is that you?
中尉 是你吗?
Malarkey?
马拉其?
Sir. Sir.
长官! 长官!
Glad to see you, sir.
真高兴见到你们
Good to see you.
你们还好吗?
Nice to see you guys.
很高兴见到你们
- Guarnere. - Sir.
- 葛奈瑞 - 是!
You and Hall up front.
你与赫尔打头阵
Who the hell is Hall?
谁是赫尔啊?
Lipton.
李普
Go.
过去
Guarnere.
葛奈瑞
Wait for my command.
等我的命令
That's enough, Guarnere!
够了 葛奈瑞!
Everyone okay?
大家都没事吗?
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
Next time I say wait for my command...
下次我说等我的命令
...you wait for my command, Sergeant.
你就等我的命令 中士
Yes, sir.
是 长官
Here you go, Lieutenant.
给你 中尉
Kraut weapon.
德国佬的武器
Fine, Quaker.
遵命 贵格教徒
What's that guy's problem?
这家伙有什么毛病?
Gonorrhea.
淋病
Really?
真的?
His name, dummy, Guarnere, gonorrhea, get it?
他的名字 傻瓜! 葛瑞奈音同"淋病"
So besides having a shitty name, what's his problem?
除了有个烂姓以外 他还有什么毛病?
None of your fucking business, Cowboy.
不关你的事 牛仔
All right, let's move out.
好了 我们出发吧
Sir.
是
Quietly.
安静点
Did you see him? He just sat there.
你看到没? 他动都不动
He didn't have a weapon.
他连武器都没有
What's he gonna do, shout at them?
怎么作战? 对敌人大叫吗?
Shouts at me for killing Krauts.
我杀德国佬他还对我大叫
He just wanted you to wait for his command.
他只是要你等他的命令
Joe, he don't even drink.
乔托伊 他甚至不喝酒
Lipton, Wynn.
李普! 怀恩!
Anybody need supplies or ammo, now's the time to get it.
需要补给物资弹药的 现在正是时候
McDowell, you okay?
麦道尔! 你还好吧?
Yes, Sergeant.
我很好 士官
Then let's go.
那就快点
Hey, I promised my kid brother I'd fetch him back a Luger.
我承诺我弟弟 给他一把鲁格枪
So I got first dibs, okay?
所以第一个战利品是我的
Check that one.
查看那个人
It's the Navy.
是海军
The landings have started, let's go.
登陆战开始了 我们走吧
- Let's move it out. - Right on time.
- 我们前进吧! - 真准时
Yeah, tell that to him, Cowboy.
是吗? 去跟死人说吧 牛仔
My name's Hall.
我的名字是赫尔
That so?
是这样吗?
Let's move out.
我们前进
You just gotta learn to return his fire.
你得学习回敬他的火气
You gotta realize it ain't about you.
这不是针对你个人
He just heard his...
他刚听到他哥哥...
Malarkey, shut your yap.
马拉其 给我住嘴
His brother got it at Cassino.
他哥哥在蒙地卡西诺阵亡
Found out before we jumped.
他在跳伞之前收到消息
'Morning, sir.
早安 长官
Battalion sure will be happy to see you guys.
营部会很高兴看到你们
Where?
在哪里?
At the farm, sir.
农场里 长官
Top of the morning to you fellows. Enjoying the war?
还喜欢这场战争吗?
Where are you from, son?
你从哪里来 孩子?
Eugene, Oregon.
奥瑞冈州尤金市
Eugene? You gotta be kidding me.
尤金? 开玩笑吧?
Popeye, did you hear this?
普派 听到没?
I'm from Astoria.
我是亚士托利亚人
You don't say.
真是巧!
Yeah, Orange Street.
是啊! 桔街~
What gives? What are you doing in a Kraut uniform?
你怎么会穿德国佬的制服?
Volksdeutsche.
德国后裔
Come again?
你说啥?
My family answered the call.
我家人回应祖国召唤
All true Aryans should return to the fatherland.
所有日耳曼人都该回归祖国
Joined up in '41.
41年加入的
You're shitting me, right?
你在开玩笑吧?
Hey, Malarkey, stop fraternizing with the enemy.
马拉其! 别再和敌人称兄道弟了
Get over here!
给我过来!
What got you to Eugene?
你怎么会去尤金市?
I was born in Eugene.
我在那里出生
Really?
真的?
Popeye.
普派
Hey, Popeye.
嘿~普派!
Hey, Harry.
嘿~哈利!
Carry on.
继续工作
Oh, Easy Company.
是Ｅ连耶
Welcome.
欢迎
Good to see you.
很高兴见到你们
And this here's Hall, Able Company.
这位是赫尔 Ａ连的
Known as Cowboy.
别名牛仔
You from Texas?
德州来的?
Manhattan.
曼哈顿
Hey boss, how you doing?
头儿 还好吧?
What's going on?
怎么了?
What's the hold up?
为何停下来?
Not sure.
不太清楚
Five will get you ten it has to do with that.
大概大家都想多歇一会儿
Yeah.
是啊
It's good to see you, Dick.
很高兴见到你 迪克
Yeah, you too, Buck.
我也是 巴克
What's the situation?
现在是什么状况?
Not good.
不好
Ninety percent of the men are still unaccounted for.
90%的人还找不到
Lieutenant Meehan?
米汉中尉呢?
No, no one's seen him, or anyone from his plane.
没看到 也没看到同机的人
You know, if he is missing...
如果他失踪了
...wouldn't that put you in line to be the next commander of Easy?
你不就是Ｅ连的最高长官?
Hey, Lieutenant Speirs.
史毕尔中尉
How many men have Dog Company got assembled?
Ｄ连集合了多少人?
A handful, maybe 20.
有一些 大约20人
You the only officer that made it?
你是唯一存活的军官?
So far.
目前是的
Still waiting for orders.
我还在等待命令
You got some cigarettes?
你有香烟吗?
Here.
给
Hey, keep the pack.
整包留着吧
Yeah, so I was in the plant in '39.
39年时我在兵工厂
That's when I was at Monarch tooling propeller shafts.
那是我在莫纳奇加工传动轴
No kidding.
真是想不到
What are the chances of that?
实在太巧合
You and me 100 miles from each other...
我们两个相距约一百里
...working at practically the same job.
竟然在做相同的工作
Hey, Malark, we're waiting on you.
马拉其! 我们在等你!
Yeah, I'm coming.
我来了
Well, I gotta run, I'll see you around.
我得走了! 下次再见!
Yeah, see you around.
好 下次再见!
Zigaretten?
香烟?
Here you go.
给你
Danke.
谢谢
Shit.
该死
Easy Company?
Ｅ连?
Hey, any of you guys know where Easy Company is?
有人知道Ｅ连在哪里吗?
You seen Lt. Meehan?
你有看到米汉中尉吗?
No, not yet.
还没有
Well, Major Strayer wants Easy Company's C.O. up front.
史戴尔少校要Ｅ连长官到前面集合
Well, I guess that means you, Dick.
那就是你啦 迪克
Come on.
走吧!
Son of a bitch.
王八蛋..
Hey, Malark, where's the best chow?
马拉其 柏林哪家餐厅最好?
In Berlin.
在柏林的哪里?
And the MGs?
机枪在哪里?
I'd say right around here, sir.
应该在附近
I can't be sure.
但我不确定
There's some Kraut 88s up ahead.
前面有88毫米炮
Up ahead and to the right about, what, 300 yards?
大约在前面300码附近吧
Up through those gardens.
在那些花园那里
They're right between us and Causeway Number Two.
他们就在我们与二号堤道之间
Firing on to the boys landing at Utah.
正朝犹他海滩上的兄弟部队开火
Think Easy can handle it?
Ｅ连能处理他们吗?
Yes, sir.
可以的 长官
'Cause my guess is they're doing some terrible damage there.
我想他们在那里重创我们
The 88s we've been hearing...
有人看到传说中的88毫米炮
...have been spotted in a field, down the road aways.
在这条路过去的空地
Major Strayer wants us to take them out.
史戴尔少校要我们清除它们
There are two guns that we know of firing on Utah Beach...
我们知道有两门炮朝犹他海滩开火
...and plan on a third and a fourth...
这里应该还有第三与第四门
...here and here.
在这里和这里
The Germans are in the trenches with access to the entire battery...
德国人躲在可通向所有炮台的壕沟里
...and with machine-gun cover in the rear.
后面还有机枪掩护
We'll establish a base of fire...
我们要建立火力支撑点
...and move under it hard and fast with two squads of three.
然后两个三人小组要在掩护下快速移动
How many Krauts they think we're facing?
我们要对付多少德国佬?
No idea.
不知道
No idea?
不知道?
We'll take some TNT along with us to spike the guns.
我们会带些炸药一起去炸掉那些炮!
Lipton, your responsibility.
李普 这由你负责
Yes, sir.
是 长官!
Liebgott, you'll take the first machine gun...
李高特! 你与派提解决第一挺机枪
...with Petty, A gunner.
他是射手
Plesha, Hendrix, you take the other.
普利夏 韩德斯 你们负责解决第二挺机枪
Who does that leave?
我们还有谁?
Compton, Malarkey, Toye, Guarnere.
康普顿! 马拉其 托伊 葛奈瑞!
Okay.
好
We'll be making the main assault.
我们进行主要攻击
Understood?
了解吗?
Yes, sir.
是 长官
All right, let's pack it up, boys.
很好 收拾行囊吧 兄弟们
Shouldn't you be outside with the other Able Company guys?
你该与其他Ａ连的人一起吧?
See you around, Hall.
再见了 赫尔
Lipton, when you see we've captured the first gun...
李普! 当你看到我们攻占第一门炮
...I want you and your TNT as fast as possible.
我要你尽快带着炸药来
Yes, sir.
是 长官!
Okay, just weapons and ammo, drop everything else.
只拿武器和弹药 放下其他东西
Got any spare ammo in a pack or a musette bag bring it along.
将多余弹药收成一包 或装入行军囊带着走
Lieutenant, sir?
中尉 我在想
I was wondering, sir, you need an extra hand?
你需要人帮忙吗?
Ain't you Sink's jeep driver?
你不是辛克的吉普车司机吗?
So?
是又怎样?
Oh, shit.
该死
What's your name, trooper?
你叫什么名字 士兵?
Lorraine, sir.
罗连 长官
You're with me, Lorraine.
你跟着我 罗连
Compton, second squad.
康普顿 第二班
Yes, sir.
是 长官
All right, you heard the word, let's move, let's move.
好 你们都听到命令了 出发...
Three cannons.
三门大炮
Petty, we've got escalating fire.
派提 前方有敌人火力
Right, let's go.
走吧!
Stay down.
趴低!
MG-42s.
42型机枪
I'll draw their fire to the right from the truck.
我从卡车那里引他们向右开枪
Take two men and hit them from the left.
带两人从左边攻击他们
Okay, go.
好 出发
Right.
好的!
Take Ranney, envelop right, give covering fire.
带着兰尼 从右边包抄 开枪掩护他们
Lorraine, on the machine gun.
罗连 你负责机枪
Don't give away your position until you have to.
非到必要时不要暴露位置
And I want that TNT as soon as we've captured the first gun. Go.
你一看到第一门炮被攻下 就马上带炸药来 去!
Yes, sir.
是 长官!
Go.
开始
I can't see nothing.
我什么也看不见
Come on, Buck.
快点 巴克
Oh, shit!
糟糕
Let's go!
快点!
Follow me!
跟着我!
Oh, fuck!
该死
It got my ass!
他打到了我屁股 我好痛
Sorry, sir.
抱歉 长官
Jesus Christ!
天啊!
Fucking jeep jockey.
开车的笨蛋
Shit, I'm sorry, sir.
抱歉 长官!
I screwed up.
我搞砸了!
Grenade!
手榴弹!
Joe, Joe, roll on, roll on!
乔! 趴下去!
God!
天啊~
Shit.
该死!
You are one lucky bastard, Joe.
你真是狗屎运 乔
Guarnere, Malarkey, Lorraine, secure that gun!
葛奈瑞、马拉其、罗连 看好这门炮
Compton, covering fire.
康普顿 开火掩护
Yes, sir!
是 长官!
Where are you hit, Pop?
你哪里被击中 普派?
I can't believe I fucked up. My ass, sir.
真是不敢相信 我屁股被击中了 长官
Your ass?
你屁股?
Oh, shit.
天啊~
Popeye, how bad is it?
普派 伤得重吗?
Sorry, sir, I didn't mean to fuck up.
抱歉 长官 我并不想搞砸
I don't think it's too bad.
我想不太严重
Can you make it back yourself?
你可以自己一个人回去吗?
I think so, sir.
我想可以的
Let's move out.
我们前进
Right, here we go.
对 我们走吧
Drop your weapon, Pop, drop your weapon.
留下你的武器 普派
Come on!
快点
One, two, three!
一、二、三!
Get down, Dick, get down!
趴下 迪克!
Pop!
普派!
Popeye, get down!
普派 趴下!
Winters, 1:00!
温斯特 一点钟!
Grenade!
手榴弹!
Toye!
托伊!
Let's go! Get out of there!
我们走! 赶快离开这里!
Get out of there!
赶快离开这里!
Toye!
托伊!
Joe!
乔!
Jesus Christ.
天啊..
Fucking twice.
居然两次..
Jesus Christ!
天啊!
Lorraine, through, go!
罗连 穿过去! 快!
Malark!
马拉其!
Ranney, let's move!
兰尼! 我们走!
They've got the first gun.
他们抢到第一门炮了
There's the second gun.
第二门炮在那里
Grenades first.
先用手榴弹
Then keep going, go!
然后继续进攻 走!
Right.
好的
Okay.
好了
Nicht schieBen!
(德语)
No make dead!
别杀我!
Shut up.
住嘴
Nicht schieBen!
(德语)
Shut the fuck up! No make dead.
给我住嘴! 别杀我!
Stay down, stay down!
趴下!
Compton!
康普顿!
All right, cover for me.
很好 掩护我!
We must be doing something right.
我们一定做对了什么
They're so confused they're firing on their own gun.
你看 他们糊涂到向自己的第三门炮开火
Let's blow this before they realize what's happening.
我们最好在他们搞清楚前将这东西炸掉
I'll see what's keeping Lip.
我去看看李普怎么还没来
All right.
好的
Toye, cover Lieutenant!
托伊 掩护中尉!
I think one of those dead Krauts has a Luger.
那个死掉的德国佬可能有鲁格手枪
So what?
那又怎样?
Keep your head low, Petty.
把头低下 派提
Come on, move it!
快点 快过去!
Have a little suppress in fire, why don't you?
开火掩护我好吗?
Jesus Christ!
我的天!
Malarkey!
马拉其!
Now you stop firing?
怎么不开枪了?
Beautiful.
好极了
Shit.
该死!
They must think he's a medic or something.
他们一定以为他是医疗兵
He's gonna need a goddamn medic.
他现在可需要医疗兵了
Okay, okay, okay.
好了 好了 好了..
Malarkey!
马拉其!
Get low!
放低姿势!
What the hell are you doing? Come on!
你在干什么? 快点!
Forgot your frigging Luger?
忘了你的鲁格枪?
You want I should go get it for you, you stupid Mick?
要我帮你去拿吗? 笨蛋
Where's Lipton with that TNT?
李普和炸药呢?
Don't know, sir.
不知道 长官
You'll be all right.
你会没事的 普派
I'm sorry, I messed up.
抱歉 我搞砸了
Don't be sorry.
别担心
Hey, Sarge?
士官?
You think this is a ticket home?
这样就要被送回家了吗?
Maybe.
或许
Shit, I just got here.
可恶 我才刚来这里
Hiya, Cowboy.
你好 牛仔
Shut your fucking Guinea trap, Gonorrhea.
给我闭上你的狗嘴 葛奈瑞
He's all right, that kid.
他其实是好人
You got a whole Kraut platoon out there.
天啊 外面有整排的德军
Probably more, Captain.
可能更多 中尉
You need help?
需要帮忙吗?
I need ammo, sir, lots of it!
我们需要弹药 长官 很多的弹药
And TNT!
还有炸药
I've got TNT, sir.
我有炸药 长官
Good job, Private.
很好 士兵
Hall, ready!
赫尔 准备好没?
Sir, I don't have any way to set it off, sir.
长官 我没办法引爆炸药
Fire in the hole!
炸弹要爆炸了!
Plesha, covering fire.
普利夏! 掩护射击
Third gun, here!
第三门炮 那里!
Lorraine, grab some more of those potato mashers and follow me.
罗连 带着炸药跟我走
Malarkey, Hall, you two, go!
马拉其 赫尔 你们两个 走!
Running a little low on ammo, sir.
弹药不太够了 长官
How about you, Malarkey?
你呢 马拉其?
Okay.
我很好!
Think you got enough to take the third gun?
你有足够弹药攻下第三门炮吗?
We'll soon find out, Dick.
等一下就知道了 迪克
Malarkey, let's go!
马拉其 我们走!
Toye, cover!
托伊 掩护我们!
Okay, Hall, keep your head down.
好 赫尔! 把头低下!
Hall!
赫尔!
Leave your TNT!
留下炸药!
Fire in the hole!
炸弹要炸了!
Malarkey, cover the front!
马拉其 负责前方
Go to the cannon, go.
去大炮那里 快点!
Hey, Sarge. I'm looking for Battalion HQ.
嘿~士官! 我在找营部指挥部
Are you kidding?
你开什么玩笑?
It's back thataway.
在后面那个方向
You mean over...
你是说...
Fire in the hole!
炸弹要炸了!
TNT!
炸药!
Don't need it.
不需要了!
What?
什么?
Hall!
赫尔!
Hall?
赫尔?
Where'd he come from?
他怎么来的?
Winters, Hester said you needed ammo!
温特斯! 海斯特说你需要弹药!
Malarkey!
马拉其!
As much as you can, everyone!
尽量拿! 所有人都一样!
You mind if D Company takes a shot at the next gun?
可以让Ｄ连试试攻占下一门炮吗?
All yours.
你请便
Let's go, Dog Company!
我们上 Ｄ连!
Up and at them, D Company.
上前进攻 Ｄ连
Compton!
康普顿!
Who is that, Speirs?
那是谁? 史毕尔吗?
What's he doing out of the trench?
他离开壕沟干什么?
Oh, what the hell's he doing?
天啊 他在做什么?
Oh, Jesus.
我的天
Sir, had a little trouble...
长官! 我在通过第一块空地时
...getting through that first field.
遇到了麻烦
Oh, Christ.
哦 天
We're gonna need it at the next gun.
我们攻下门炮时会很需要
Once it's blown, have them leave.
一旦炸掉赶快撤退
Go! Yes, sir.
是 长官!
Compton, police them both, then pull out!
康普顿 掩护他们两个 然后撤退!
Lorraine, Toye, move out!
罗连 托伊 撤退!
Move out!
撤退!
Move out! Move it out!
撤退! 撤退!
MGs first.
机枪先撤
Fall back to your original positions.
机枪退守原来位置
Everyone else, maintain your base of fire.
其他人开火掩护
Okay, back to battalion!
好 回到营部去 走!
Go, go!
快走!
They were 105s, not 88s, sir.
那是105毫米 不是88毫米
We disabled them and pulled out.
我们毁掉它们后撤退了
I figure there's maybe 40 or so Krauts...
我想大概还有40名德国佬
...still manning three MG-42s to the rear.
仍在后方守着三挺42型机枪
Hey, Popeye.
普派!
Forty?
40个?
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
We killed maybe around 20...
我们大约杀了20个
...so, yeah, probably there's 40 left.
所以..大约还有40个
I think we need artillery...
我想我们需要大炮
...or maybe mortars might do the job.
或是迫击炮才能完成任务
Going my way?
要搭便车吗?
Sure.
是的
Sergeant.
长官
Careful, don't hurt yourself.
小心! 别受伤了!
Nice ride you got here, Nix.
你的车挺不错的 尼克森
Straight from Utah Beach.
直接从犹他海滩运来的
We should put them to work before they're missed.
趁还能动时尽量用
By nightfall...
入夜后
...Second Battalion had secured Sainte-Marie-du-Mont...
第二营攻下圣梅莉山头
...and elements of the 4th Division were beginning to move men and material inland.
第四师已开始移动人员与物资进入内陆
Most of the 101st Airborne, including Easy Company...
大部分101空降师 包括Ｅ连
...were still scattered all over Normandy...
仍散落在整个诺曼底区
...and the success of the invasion was far from certain.
而我们离入侵成功还远的很
We had an hour to rest...
我们有一小时休息
...and scrounge for food we could...
并尽量收集食物
...before we had to move south...
然后就得向南前进
...and secure the town of Courville.
攻下库柏小镇
...die in the back of this damn truck.
我才不要死在这卡车上
Come on, you're stepping on my legs.
你踩着我脚了
Jesus, let me out of here.
天啊! 让我下车!
Light, light discipline.
灯光 灯光管制
Guarnere, close that flap.
葛奈瑞 把帐幕放下
Let the Krauts cook their own goddamn food.
让德国人自己去烤食物
How are we doing, Malark?
大家状况如何 马拉其?
We're doing good.
我们没问题
Doing good?
-很好? 　-是的
What the hell do you know about cooking, you're Irish.
你怎么会懂得烹饪 你是爱尔兰人?
Sir, if you have a reservation someplace else...
长官 如果你在别处订了位置
Just start dishing it.
把菜端出来就是了
Thank you.
谢谢你
Shit.
该死
Jesus Christ, give me some air.
这里臭气冲天 让我透口气
'Evening.
晚安
Hello, sir.
你好 长官
Did something die in here?
有东西死在这里吗?
Yeah, Malarkey's ass.
是啊 马拉其的屁股
Any word on Lieutenant Meehan, sir?
有米汉中尉的消息吗 长官?
No, not yet.
还没有
Don't that make you our commanding officer, sir?
那你不就成为我们的指挥官?
Yeah, it does.
是的
Sir?
长官?
Joe, the Lieutenant don't drink.
乔 中尉不喝酒的
It's been a day of firsts.
今天第一次的经验还真多
Don't you think, Guarnere?
不是这样吗 葛奈瑞?
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
Carry on.
你们继续吧
Good night, sir.
晚安 长官
Oh, Sergeant?
士官?
Sir?
是的
I'm not a Quaker.
我不是贵格教徒
If he's from Lancaster County, he's probably a Mennonite.
若他是从兰卡斯特郡来的 他可能是门诺派教徒
What's a Mennonite?
什么是门诺派教徒?
Hey, wait up!
迪克!
What?
怎样?
You know that map you found?
记得你找到的地图吗?
It had every Kraut gun in Normandy on it.
那上面有德国佬在诺曼底每挺机枪的位置
Oh, yeah?
是吗?
Yeah.
是啊
Here.
我来
Don't ever get a cat.
看来你没养过猫
What's on your mind?
你在想什么?
I lost a man today.
我今天失去一名弟兄
Hall.
赫尔
Thanks.
谢了
A John Hall, New Yorker.
他叫约翰·赫尔 纽约人
Got killed today at Brecourt.
今天在布里克被杀
I never knew him.
我没机会认识他
Yeah, you did.
你认识的
Radio-op, 506th basketball team, Able Company.
通讯兵 506团蓝球队的 Ａ连
He was a good man.
他是个好男人
Man.
男人
Not even old enough to buy a beer.
根本连喝酒年龄都还没到
Not hungry.
我不饿
Hey, Dick.
迪克
I sent that map up to Division.
我要送那地图到师部
I think it's gonna do some good.
我想它会有点用处
That night I took time to thank God...
那晚我向上帝感恩
...for seeing me through that day of days...
谢谢他那天眷顾着我
...and prayed I would make it through D plus one.
还祈求保佑我撑到登陆第二日
And if, somehow, I managed to get home again...
如果 我真能够撑到回家
...I promised God, and myself...
我答应上帝 还有我自己
...that I would find a quiet piece of land someplace...
我会找个安静的地方
...and spend the rest of my life in peace.
平静度过余生